module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Within Accenture, what does CAL stand for?',
    a: 'Customer Acquisition Lead',
    b: 'Client Account Lead',
    c: 'Committee Accord Leaflet',
    d: 'Customer Action Legend',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Clearhead analytics, what does MDE mean?',
    a: 'Minimum Decrease Equation',
    b: 'Maximum Detectable Effect',
    c: 'Minimum Detectable Effect',
    d: 'Maximum Determinable Evaluation',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In business, EPS is shorthand for what?',
    a: 'Earnings Per Share',
    b: 'Earnings Per Solution',
    c: 'Employees Per State',
    d: 'Employees Per Sector',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
   question: 'In computer software, what does API stand for?',
    a: 'Application Program Interface',
    b: 'Application Peer Interaction',
    c: 'Application Program Interactions',
    d: 'Apparel Program Indicator',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What tool does MME stand for in the Accenture world?',
    a: 'Manage My Expenses',
    b: 'Manage My Emotions',
    c: 'Manage My Engagements',
    d: 'Merge My Expenses',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'On the internet, HTTP stands for ____.',
    a: 'Hypertext Tool Protocol',
    b: 'Hypertext Transfer Protocol',
    c: 'Highway Text Tool Protocol',
    d: 'Highfrequency Text Transfer Program',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In marketing, CRM is the acronym for what?',
    a: 'Customer Relationship Management',
    b: 'Content Record Management',
    c: 'Consumer Relationship Manager',
    d: 'Customer Record Merger',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Accenture, MYTE is shorthand for what tool?',
    a: 'My Time is Everything',
    b: 'My Time and Expenses',
    c: 'My Tits and Ass',
    d: 'My Time and Experience',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In the Internets, URL is short for what?',
    a: 'Universal Record Locator',
    b: 'Universal Record Legend',
    c: 'Universal Resource Locator',
    d: 'Universe Resource Legend',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'In computer software, RAM is an acronym for what?',
    a: 'Results At Moments Notice',
    b: 'Rich Access Memory',
    c: 'Random Access Memory',
    d: 'Rich Access Mechanism',
    answer: 'c'
  }
];
